{"data":[{"question":"It is important that the nature ___.","a":"can be protected","b":"will be protected","c":"are being protected","d":"shall be protected","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Zero Conditional: used for habitual actions or accepted facts \n- It is created by if\/when + two clauses with the same tense in each clause.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Without the ozone layer to shield from part of the sun's UV rays, the earth during the day ___, too hot for us to live.","a":"will be boiling hot","b":"would be boiling hot","c":"can boil hotly","d":"would be boiled hot","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 2: used to talk about unlikely, imaginary or untrue events or situations \n- Form: if + Simple Past, would + Infinitive ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Jim and Tim _________ last night, but they went to the party instead.","a":"must have studied","b":"might study","c":"would study","d":"should have studied","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Should have PP: used for saying what was the right thing to do when you realize that someone did not do it","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"___ , humans could not live at all.","a":"If it was for the sun","b":"Were it not for the sun","c":"If it shouldn't be for the sun","d":"Had it not been for the sun","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Sometimes conditional forms are inverted as a means of sounding more formal. In this case, the conditional 'if' is dropped and the inverted forms takes the place of the 'if clause' \n- Inversion clause: auxiliary + subject + main verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The adviser's suggestion that Sandra ___ till next Monday is reasonable.","a":"are waiting","b":"wait","c":"would wait","d":"will wait","answer":"2","explain":"\n- The Subjunctive is used to emphasize urgency or importance. It is used after certain expressions: \n - S+ advise \/ask\/to command\/demand\/desire\/insist\/propose\/recommend\/request\/suggest\/ urge (that) + S + (would) Infinitive","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The experiment had failed. \"I suggest you ___ again.\"","a":"trying","b":"try","c":"would try","d":"will try","answer":"2","explain":"\n- The Subjunctive is used to emphasize urgency or importance. It is used after certain expressions: \n - S+ advise \/ask\/to command\/demand\/desire\/insist\/propose\/recommend\/request\/suggest\/ urge (that) + S + (would) Infinitive","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"We ___ the work so fast without your help.","a":"don't have got through the customs","b":"hadn't had got through the customs","c":"couldn't have got through the customs","d":"can't have got through the customs","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Could have PP: used to say that something was a possibility in the past, but did not actually happen\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"You ___ the bus; however, you got there a little late.","a":"should catch","b":"could catch","c":"would have caught","d":"must have caught","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Would have PP: used when talking about something that did not happen, or a situation that cannot exist","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I wish they ___ that trouble again when they ___ this afternoon.","a":"would not bring up, come","b":"will not bring up, will come","c":"will not bring up, come","d":"would not bring up, would come","answer":"1","explain":"\n- A wish about the past: Wish clause,had PP\/ should, could have PP ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The order came that the daily necessities ___ to the disaster area soon.","a":"should send","b":"would be sent","c":"must be sent","d":"be sent","answer":"4","explain":"\n- The Subjunctive is used to emphasize urgency or importance. It is used after certain expressions: \n - S+ advise \/ask\/to command\/demand\/desire\/insist\/propose\/recommend\/request\/suggest\/ urge (that) + S + (would) Infinitive ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"69","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}